is
bag alloy there in the stall me you and Caio
for us to talk
that new marketing strategy there
what is the idea here that we are cheating bro
cool guys who like jazz like wine
likes to skate likes to
let's show something
She's modified but modified only Got you
Somewhere Half The Time
And The Other Half Even Got You
normal little street commerce
it doesn't even give anything
then you come in here
has 1 secret door that is no longer secret
wanted to present
for you there the brownie
see if it makes sense then we put it here in the house
brownies brownies tá
makes a lot of sense
for us by the public
really works well in the face of the curl
it's coming to us this week brother
only it's the mocap of the new
it's on,
that's not the whole one but the mocap
to do
you see what he sent me count
we're negotiating here i think it will be good
message to wesley my manager
for him
unroll with you there but now you can leave the brownies
This is not over
just closed
melou wine and shit
let me see let me see ahead
Sunday night walking a brownie in his wallet
to bring the art of development